Hello my name is Jonathan Samir Matthis and I am a professor of neuroscience in Boston
Massachusetts USA Now it's a rather long story but these days I spend most of my time building
free open source software based on technologies that I am familiar with as a result of my
scientific research And this is one of them So what you should be seeing is a transcription of
the words that I'm saying in English and then the translation of those words into several other
languages below And if you pause the video at any point in time it should be highlighting the word
I'm currently saying in English and then the closest matching word in the translations below
Let's give that a quick test 1 2 3 4 5 Red blue green yellow pink My dad is from Texas
my mom is from Syria my brother is named Paul and I have two cats named Poo and Ollie Which
way is the library Okay thank you nice to meet you So that's the basic idea If you speak any of
these languages please let me know how it goes especially in the word highlight matching thing
And if you're interested in this project I would love to develop it so let me know